The day the world catches fire
Supernova is a science fiction, action, drama film directed by John Harrison.
A international science conference is held in Australia when Dr.
Austin Shepard mysteriously disappears.
Shepard's colleague, Christopher Richardson and other people are soon faced with the reality
of an impending crisis and an attempt to keep the information from the public.
While a full-blown supernova does not occur, explosions on the sun cause massive damage in Australia,
and is shown often in Sydney and in various other cities and countries of the world.
Lisa Delgado, played by Tia Carrere.
Haley Richardson, played by Eliza Bennett.
Laurie Stephenson, played by Emma Samms.
Dr. Austin Shepard, played by Peter Fonda.
Dr. Chris Richardson, played by Luke Perry.
Ginny McKillip, played by Clemency Burton-Hill.
Supernova is a 2005 television miniseries directed by John Harrison and
featuring an ensemble cast led by Luke Perry and Peter Fonda.
It originally aired on the Hallmark Channel.
The series is of the disaster genre and has a large number of special effects.
It was filmed on location in Cape Town, South Africa and Sydney, Australia.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.